One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Let's travel all through the worldwide seas,
raising our battle cry.
If you've made up your mind, let the signal for departure
ring out.
We were able to escape from the set course
along the boundary between sky and sea.
Now we're rowing our way
to a hidden adventure at the dark bottom of the sea.
Doesn't it sound fun just thinking about it?
Let's travel all through the worldwide seas,
raising our battle cry.
If you've made up your mind, let the signal for departure
ring out.
That feeling we had when we set sail
is something I'll never forget.
Because of that
nothing will be able to scare me...
Now, as the trip approaches, our racing heartbeats
engrave a rhythm of adventure in our shy hearts.
Get all the treasures
while laughing out loud.
Give them all out at a big party
making a splash...
Fill your empty heart with dreams.
Spread your wings.
If you color your heart with the blowing wind
you will move on.
Get all the treasures
while laughing out loud.
Give them all out at a big party
making a splash...
Number 900?!
Lola's Pursuit and the Humming Swordsman
Hey, what're you doing newcomer?!
It's impossible for us, zombies, to betray our master's orders...
How come he's disobeying?!
Moreover, he's as powerful as a general grade!
Put simply, that unstoppable power...
The power to make the impossible possible...
The name of the hurricane that knocks down all obstacles is...!
Love!
As I thought, all those ridiculous things that Dog Penguin is saying...
Are almost like Sanji's.
Hey, Dog Penguin!
Do you know something about Sanji?!
We're Sanji's friends, so...
Shut the hell up, pirates!
He's our enemy after all!
What?
Now what?!
Wait, Lola!
A wild boar?
Hey!
Wait, Lola!
Come and catch me!
What?!
I finally found you...
Burglar Cat!
Me?!
W-Wait a minute!
I haven't stolen anything yet!
It's useless!
I won't let you have Ab-sama!
Don't lay a hand on this lady.
Don't butt in!
Dog Penguin!
Why didn't he attack?!
Even if I die...
I'll never hurt a woman!
Amazing!
To figure out that thing was a woman, you sure are something!
Usopp! Chopper!
I've got my bride!
Amazing, Nami is flying!
Idiots, I'm being kidnapped!
By who?!
Wait!
Well then, we shall start the ceremony right away!
I've already made the preparations!
Put me down!
You're the invisible man who was in the bathroom, aren't you?!
Could that be for real?!
Nami!
I've evaluated you.
You're most suitable to become my bride!
My name is Absalom!
It's the name of your future husband.
Be sure to remember it!
You've got some nerve spying on naked people!
Keeping my body in shape everyday isn't something I do just to have some perverted beast spy on it!
Thunder Charge!
Nami!
Good job!
Let's just keep running!
We're getting outta this forest!
What?!
He hasn't fallen down!
He isn't just anyone, you can tell by looking at him!
What... is this shock running through my body...?
It's as if I had just been struck by a bolt of lightning!
Perhaps... this is...
Love?
You won't get away from me!
Hey! This isn't time to stand without doing anything!
It is our job to capture those three!
You're right!
If we fail, Perona-sama's punishment awaits us!
No! They're going after that lady!
But, why am I protecting that girl?!
Moreover, I can't move...!
This body is too weak!
Hurry up and catch those three!
Wait, Wild Zombies!
Don't lay a hand on that woman!
Shut up, Perv-salom!
We receive orders from the master, but we're Perona-sama's subordinates!
I said wait!
I'm aware that you are Perona's underlings.
However...!
You should still know not to make me angry.
Don't push your luck.
What do you want?!
I won't let you... go after that lady.
H-Hey, newcomer, stop!
Don't anger Absalom!
Wait, Burglar Cat!
Hey, Nami! She seems to be only after you!
You're right! What did I do?!
Why don't we split into two groups and escape?
You wanna leave me, cold-hearted monster?!
Come here, damn it!
The wild boar is so scary!
Could it be that they...
What're you bastards doing?!
Let me out!
just like Straw Hat now, were drawn into the other side of the wall?
Monkey! Monkey!
And soon you'll share the same fate!
You have invulnerable zombies coming from both sides.
Just give it up!
I can't figure out whether you're a dumbass spider or a dumbass monkey, but...
That huge spiderweb that the Sunny got caught in when we landed was your doing, wasn't it?
That's right!
All of your actions head right to Perona-sama's Ghost Network.
I wonder if those big ears also contribute to the info gathering.
They look like they could hear very well.
What did you say just now?
Stop pretending!
It's the worst case scenario.
We're completely surrounded.
It seems we urgently need a counter-measure.
Shall I take care of this?!
Do as you wish.
I'll try to deal with it.
I'm pretty reliable actually.
Well then, let's get started!
Wait! What're you gonna do?!
Coup de...
Vent!
Wh...aaat?!
You... destroyed the bridge?!
Well, that's how it is.
As violent as always.
Cien Fleur...
One Hundred Flowers
Wing!
You! You can fly?!
Yes, for about five seconds.
Too short!
No... but it's long enough.
Strong Right!
Alright! Got it!
Now if we can just make it to that entrance, we can follow Straw Hat!
I'm sorry.
This is my limit.
Pulling arm!
Everyone seems to have fallen into the courtyard.
This doesn't mean it's over, but...
They won't follow us for now.
That went fairly well.
You bastard!
How dare you use me as a stepping stone?!
Damn you!
This is unforgivable!
I'm a spider!
I'll get back there in no time!
What is... that?
What the...?
Is something... falling?
No!
Someone is coming!
Only bones!
Bone!
Hey, stop! Stop it!
Don't kill her! She's our friend!
Bastard!
Bastard, stop!
Hurry and escape, Nami!
Absalom is gonna be my groom!
Begone!
Prepare to die!
Wa-!
Wait a minute!
I-!
I'm...!
I'm actually a man!
Hey, hey.
Is that true?!
That's right!
It's a hobby of mine!
It's no joke!
Plus...
You and that beast man are perfect for each other!
I thought I could give you all my support!
Really?!
Really!
It's no joke!
No one has ever given me such supportive thoughts before.
You're the first person to ever have said such kind words to me.
I...
I...!
Raise your head, my friend.
This is called friendship.
My name is Namizou.
You may call me Nami.
Friendship...!
Nami!
She fell for it!
Of course you can't put his seal on while he's conscious.
If you do it while he's sleeping-
Attack while he's sleeping?!
Is that ok!? As a human being?!
But, aren't you a zombie, Lola?
That's mean! It's too low!
It's alright as long as he's sleeping and doesn't notice.
Hey, Namizou.
Can we get out of here now?
By the way, Lola...
I dropped something earlier in the treasure storehouse...
I want it back but, I can't remember the way. Can you tell me?
Silly you.
But it's fine.
The closest way is right through Lady Perona's room over there.
Do you see it?
See that incredibly high tower over there?
She's completely taken in... she's not gonna come out of it.
If you go straight that way you will come across the stairs that lead to it.
So Nami was a man all along...
I always thought she acted kinda manly.
Hey Nami, that guy has caught up to us.
Really?!
Lola! Attack chance!
I'll never meet him again, so you'll be fine!
Do your best! You two will be the best couple!
Thank you, Nami!
I'm full of courage now!
Absalom!
Lola!
You two, this is our chance!
The wild boar didn't harm Nami after all.
Nami, you're incredible!
If you talk to her, you'll realize she's not so bad after all.
You have a weird look again!
Not a single treasure chest in the whole ship?!
Yes, there are some, but they're almost empty.
All that's left is just a small amount of money.
I'm surprised that these two ships gave us almost no spoils.
Is this really the ship of the man who beat Crocodile?
Well, it's fine.
Carry out some rations, if there are any.
Yes.
Perona-sama!
Hildon.
Moria-sama has summoned the Three Mystery Persons.
Master?
What for?
It seems Straw Hat Luffy has been captured.
It's time to awaken Number 900.
Number 900?!
Are you serious?!
Ab-sama!
Absalom, you bastard! Come out and marry me!
You disappeared and ran again, didn't you?!
Strange...
There's nowhere else they could have run to.
Hey, Kumashi!
Absalom-sama, I've got a problem...
Something's bothering me...
Wait, my issues come first.
Have three pirates come through here?
That's...
Absalom!
What're you doing here?
This is my room.
Perona.
Welcome back, Perona-sama...
Don't talk, Kumashi!
How many times do I have to tell you?!
But, there's something impo-
Be quiet!
Don't speak.
You are as severe as ever with Kumashi...
Sevearsy.
Quiet, he's my subordinate.
More importantly, have you heard?
Master is calling for us.
Did something happen?
Did something happen? I'll tell you what happened!
Number 900 is gonna be awakened.
The 900?!
Did he capture that 300 million man?!
Somehow, we're still barely hiding from them.
It's a miracle.
Then again, why're we hiding in such place?!
We had no choice!
I didn't think that beast man would catch up with us so fast!
Moreover, I don't think that guy's a zombie.
We'll get outta here once we get the chance, alright?
Absalom-sama!
So you were here.
I've brought interesting information.
What is it?
There's another trespasser along with the pirates.
Trespasser?
The "Humming" Chivalrous Swordsman.
What?!
Someone... fell from the sky.
Hey, what was it that fell just now?
Could it be...
Well...
I can tell by looking at the mark...
That was a strange interruption, but you're not gonna get away from me.
I can make as many footholds as I need.
Monkey! Monkey!
You, buy me some time.
What're you gonna do?
These are some fine stone pillars you have here.
I'm gonna make a little weapon.
Spider...
Sticky Net!
From the glands in his hands...
Seis Fleur...
Six Flowers
Slap!
Something touched my eye!
I'm stuck!
I got myself with the sticky net!
Alright, Nico Robin, I'm ready.
Step back.
What is that?
What, I just took the iron nunchucks I was carrying and jammed them in these pillars.
With a monster this huge, you need an equally huge weapon.
Heavy Nunchaku!
What's with his power...
Is he... actually human?
Stop it, bastard!
Spider Sticky Net!
Weapons...
Left!
Nico Robin!
What're those things?!
Mouse! Mouse!
I'm sorry...
I let my guard down.
I hadn't thought there were other spiders.
D-Damn it!
Idiots...
Monkey, Monkey...
It's not about whether you let your guard down or not.
These are my subordinates, the Spider Mice.
There are as many as 500 of them here on Thriller Bark.
We've never let even a single prey we've caught escape!
We wait everywhere to ambush. From the darkness and blind spots we capture our enemy.
Our thread has been modified by Hogback-sama so that no human strength can tear it!
From above the ceiling while in the mansion, we carried away your friends.
Now, we'll take you to the same place as your friends.
Resign yourselves!
ヨホホホー
Yohohohoo
ヨーホホーホー
Yoohoohohoo
ヨホホホー
Yohohohoo
Who is it?
Who's singing?!
ヨーホホーホー
Yoohoohohoo
ビンクスの酒を
Going to deliver Bink's sake...
届けにゆくよ海風気まかせ波まかせ
Doing as one pleases, following the sea breeze between the waves...
潮の向こうで夕日も騒ぐ
On the other side of the tide, alarmed at the setting sun...
空にゃ輪をかく鳥の唄
Drawing a circle in the sky, the song of a bird.
My, my, it seems that everyone has come to this island.
How did you get here from below?
I jumped. I'm very light after all.
If you've come, then I suppose there's no choice.
I'll tell you all about this island.
Hey, bastard! Who're you?!
You're not a zombie!
You're one of the pirates' friends, aren't you?!
Hey, skeleton!
Yes, yes.
It's alright...
I've put an end to the battle.
Three-Pace Hum:
Notch Slash!